var questionsLibrary = [
    {
        question: "What did Hagrid give Harry the first time they met?",
        answers: ["An owl", "A wand", "A birthday cake", "A pig tail"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How did Hagrid get his pet dragon, Norbert?",
        answers: ["He won him in a card game", "Found him in the Forbidden Forrest", "Received him as a gift", "Bought him in Romania"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is Harry's Patronus?",
        answers: ["Werewolf", "Stag", "Dog", "Doe"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What creature is Buckbeak?",
        answers: ["Centaur", "3 headed dog", "Unicorn", "Hippogriff"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Harry's parents live?",
        answers: ["Hogsmeade", "Godric's Hollow", "The Burrow", "Spinner's End"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "When is Harry's birthday?",
        answers: ["April 29th", "June 30th", "July 31st", "October 20th"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the Master of death?",
        answers: ["Draco Malfoy", "Lord Voldemort", "Albus Dumbledore", "Harry Potter"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which two characters share a Patronus?",
        answers: ["Harry and his father", "Severus Snape and Lily Potter", "Harry and Sirius Black", "Ron Weasley and Pettigrew"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the disreputable area of Diagon Alley?",
        answers: ["Gringotts", "Leaky Cauldron", "Imperium Alley", "Knockturn Alley"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How did Harry survive underwater in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        answers: ["Gillyweed", "Bubble-head charm", "Transfiguration", "Gills charm"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What spell is used in The Sorcerer's Stone to save Hermione from the troll?",
        answers: ["Stupify", "Wingardium Leviosa", "Lumos", "Petificus Totalus"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What was Harry's first broomstick?",
        answers: ["Firebolt", "Thunderbolt", "Nimbus 2000", "Cleansweep Two"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How did Harry spend his first detention?",
        answers: ["Cleaning trophies", "Writing an essay", "Going to the Forbidden Forest", "Signing autographs"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Fred and George's joke shop?",
        answers: ["Weasley Joke Emporium", "Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes", "Fred & George's Wonder Emporium", "Zonko's Joke Shop"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which is NOT one of the Unforgivable Curses?",
        answers: ["Crusiatus Curse", "Imperius Curse", "Sectumsempra", "Avada Kedavra"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who guards the entrance to the Gryffindor common room?",
        answers: ["The Fat Lady", "The Bloody Baron", "3 headed dog", "The Fat Friar"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What does Ron see in the Mirror of Erised?",
        answers: ["Himself marrying Hermione", "Himself with lots of money", "Himself as Harry Potter", "Himself holding the Quidditch Cup"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is a wizard the cannot do magic?",
        answers: ["Muggle", "Squib", "Mudblood", "Wizont"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Where does Hermione brew her first Polyjuice Potion?",
        answers: ["In Hagrid's Hut", "In her room", "Moaning Myrtle's Bathroom", "The Room of Requirement"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is said to close the Marauder's Map and make it blank again?",
        answers: ["Nothing to see here", "Mischief Managed", "All done", "Hello Professor"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What are the 3 kinds of ball used in Quidditch?",
        answers: ["Bludgers, Snitches, & Quaffles", "Bludgers, Snitches, Wiffles", "Bludgers, Snitches, Foozles", "Wiffles, Snitches, & Quaffles"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Who stole Harry's letters at the beginning of The Chamber of Secrets?",
        answers: ["The Dursleys", "Hagrid", "Dobby", "Draco Malfoy"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many Weasley siblings are there?",
        answers: ["5", "7", "4", "6"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What platform does the Hogwarts Express depart?",
        answers: ["eleventeen", "nine and three-quarters", "eight and one-quarter", "five and a half"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Filch's cat?",
        answers: ["Buttercup", "Mrs.Kitty", "Crookshanks", "Mrs.Norris"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is Peter Pettigrew's nickname?",
        answers: ["Wormtail", "Scabbers", "Scabby", "Ratty"],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What position in Quidditch does Harry play?",
        answers: ["Chaser", "Seeker", "Keeper", "Beater"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What does the spell Wingardium Leviosa do?",
        answers: ["Inflicts pain on a target", "turns target to stone", "Levitates an object", "gives flying powers to an object"],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Name the magical creature that transforms itself into someones worst fear.",
        answers: ["Flobberworm", "Boggart", "Bowtruckle", "Death Eater"],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What type of animal can Harry communicate with?",
        answers: ["Hippogriffs", "All animals", "Owls", "Snakes"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What guards the Azkaban prison?",
        answers: ["Boggarts", "Acromantula", "Thestrals", "Dementors"],
        correctAnswer: 3
    }
];